glprop.com 2014-04-18

# Privacy | Global Logistic Properties

## privacy

GLP is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to this website. This policy illustrates to you how GLP treats and protects information you provide when you visit this website.

### Collecting Information

In general, you can visit this website without revealing who you are or any information about yourself. Under some circumstances, the website may require you to provide individual identifiable and background information for the convenience of your visiting or for providing you services after visiting the website. You reserve the right of offering your confidential data to the website, and please do not submit your confidential data if you do not want it being collected.

Our web servers collect the domain names of visitors. Similar to many websites, our web servers also seek to place a "cookie" (a small data file) on your computer's hard drive which allows the server to determine the computer when it visits again, in order to track statistical information about navigation to and throughout certain areas of this website. This is used to help improve this website navigation and to measure the effectiveness of the overall website experience. It is not shared with anyone other than GLP affiliates and contractors who assists GLP in these efforts and are bound to confidentiality. However, if you prefer not to accept cookies, you can set your browser to reject them or to alert you before one is placed. 

### Use of Information Collected

By providing your personal information, you make it easier for GLP to make the website relevant to you, communicate with you, assist you in making a purchase of GLP products, and allow you access to certain exclusive sections of the website.

Domain name information that the website collects is not used to identify you personally and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the website, pages viewed, etc. This information is used to measure the use of the website and to improve the content of the website. When other information is collected from you, such as your name and e-mail address, we generally let you know at the time of collection how it will be used.

The personal information you provide may be stored and processed in which GLP or its affiliates conduct operations. By submitting such information, you consent to the transfer of such information outside your home country. 

### Security of Information Collected

GLP maintains strict practice to safeguard your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. 

GLP limits access to information about you to those GLP employees who need to know the information to respond to your inquiry or request. Your personal information will be kept confidential unless you clearly indicated that you agree to expose whole or parts of your personal information. Except the confidential data explicitly stated, any other information you provide to the website, such as suggestions, opinions or the like will not be regarded as confidential.

### Links to Other Websites

GLP's website may contain links to other websites, and GLP shall not be responsible for the information collection or privacy practices, or the content on those websites.

### Changes to this Policy

GLP advises to check this privacy policy periodically to keep you updated of any changes.
